wildbit.com 2019-07-01

# Privacy Policy | Wildbit

**Last amended: April 9, 2019**  

**Effective Date:** ******April 9, 2019**

This Privacy Policy applies to the websites: [](http://www.privacyshield.gov/)www.wildbit.com, [www.beanstalkapp.com](http://www.beanstalkapp.com/), [www.conveyor.com](https://conveyor.com/), and [www.postmarkapp.com](http://www.postmarkapp.com/) (the “Sites”) owned and operated by Wildbit, LLC (collectively, “Wildbit”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). This Privacy Policy describes how Wildbit collects, uses, shares and secures the personal information you provide, as well as the information about our customers' customers or end users that we process on behalf of our customers. It also describes your choices regarding use, access, correction and deletion of your personal information.

## 1\. EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks 

Wildbit, LLC complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework [as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce](http://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome) regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and the United Kingdom and Switzerland, as applicable to the United States in reliance on Privacy Shield. Wildbit, LLC has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov/](http://www.privacyshield.gov/). 

Wildbit is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under each Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Wildbit complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions. Wildbit is liable for any processing of personal information by such third parties that is inconsistent with the Privacy Shield Principles unless it is not responsible for the event giving rise to any alleged damage. 

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, Wildbit is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Wildbit may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Wildbit, LLC commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Wildbit, LLC at: 

_Natalie Nagele, CEO,[natalie@wildbit.com](mailto:natalie@wildbit.com). 225 Chestnut St, Philadelphia, PA 19106. Phone: 215-203-0488._

Wildbit, LLC has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, you may visit [https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-...](https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield) for more information or to file a complaint (free of charge). To facilitate fast and convenient resolution of complaints, you agree to participate in on-line dispute resolution through JAMS Online Mediation (Endispute). 

Under certain conditions, Privacy Shield provides the right to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have not provided resolution. This is described in [Annex I to the Privacy Shield](http://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction).

## 2\. How we Collect Information: 

We collect the following personal information from you: 

### 2.1 Information that you provide to us about yourself

When you sign up for the Services, we ask you for information such as 

  * Contact Information, such as name, email address, mailing address, or phone number; 
  * Demographic information, such as age, education, gender, interests and zip code 
  * Billing Information, such as credit card number and billing address; 
  * Unique Identifiers, such as username, account number or password; 
  * IP address; 
  * Information about your business, such as company name, company size, business type.

If you do not provide this information, we will not be able to provide the Services to you. 

### 2.2 Information you provide to us about your customers, end users, and contacts

For the provision of our Services to you, you provide us with information which may identify your customers, end users or employees. Such information includes: 

  * Email addresses;
  * IP addresses;
  * Content of emails sent through Postmark.

You may also provide us personal information about your contacts such as Name and email address where we can send receipts of your purchases. When you provide us with personal information about your contacts we will only use this information for the specific reason for which it is provided. If you believe that one of your contacts has provided us with your personal information and you would like to request that it be removed from our database, please contact us at the contact information below. 

### 2.3 Information collected automatically 

When you use our Services, we use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about your location, and your activities on our website, information about your device and log information. This is described in more detail below. These cookies and similar technologies collect anonymized Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. 

Wildbit allows Google Analytics and Snowplow Analytics to use these technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole for the purpose of analytics. 

You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service. We do not use, or allow the use of cookies or similar technologies in connection with your customers' data. 

_Google Analytics:_

We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect some information we listed above about your use of the Services. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to improve the Services and to help you improve your Application. In order to collect this information, Google Analytics may set cookies on your browser or mobile device, or read cookies that are already there. Google Analytics may also receive information about you from apps you have downloaded, that partner with Google. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Services to another application which partners with Google, is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. Please review those and see [http://www.google.com/policies...](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) for information about how Google uses the information provided to Google Analytics and how you can control the information provided to Google. To prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, you can download the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on for Google Analytics which can be found [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

## 3\. Purpose and Legal basis of the Processing

To the extent EU data protection law applies to our processing of information about you, we act as the "data controller". To the extent EU data protection law applies to our processing of your customer or end user data, you serve as the "data controller" or "data processor" and we serve as the "data processor" or "data sub-processor". 

_To perform the Services:_ We use your information to identify you, process your payment, provide you with technical support and assistance; and communicate with you about the Services via email. For example we will contact you to notify you of any issues with the Services or any suspicious activity in your account. The legal basis for these uses in the performance of the contract with you. 

_To Optimize or improve the Services:_ We use your information to authenticate you, prevent fraud and abuse of our Services and perform research. The legal basis for these uses is our legitimate interest in the improvement and optimization of our service offerings and in ensuring the security of our services and we apply appropriate safeguards to protect your information (see Section 5 below). 

## 4\. How we Share your Information 

We share information with service providers, as required by law, and in connection with the protection and enforcement of our legal and contractual rights. 

_With Service Providers:_ We share your information with third parties who provide services on our behalf to help with our business activities. This includes: payment processing, providing customer service, sending marketing communications (this does not include information about your customers), conducting research and analysis and providing cloud computing infrastructure. The legal basis for sharing this information is our legitimate interest in providing our Services efficiently and we implement measure to safeguard your information. 

_With Public Authorities or Law Enforcement:_ In certain situations, Wildbit may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We may also disclose your personal information as required by law (such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process), when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, when we believe there is a violation to our Terms of Service (see Postmark Terms of Service, Beanstalk Terms of Service), to protect your safety or the safety of others, to investigate fraud, to respond to a government request, if we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, or if we are involved in a bankruptcy or liquidation proceeding. The legal basis for this is our legitimate interest in protecting our legal rights and those of others, compliance with legal obligations and our legitimate interest in fulfilling legal obligations imposed by legal authorities outside of the EU. _  
_

_Prevent fraud and abuse of the Services:_ We will share information to prevent or detect fraud or to address technical issues and if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding situations that involve abuse of the Services infrastructure. The legal basis for this is our legitimate interest in the maintaining the security of our Services. 

We also process and share information in an aggregated, de-identified manner, where the information is shared as part of a statistical report and does not contain personal information. 

## 5\. Security 

The security of your personal information is important to us. We implement adequate measures to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. Wildbit, LLC takes steps to ensure that all source code, files and data remain private and confidential. Due to the sensitive nature of source code we take this very seriously and make it our primary concern for all customers. We restrict access to personal information to Wildbit employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our service. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at the contact information below. 

## 6\. Rights with respect to your information

Upon request Wildbit will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access, correct, obtain a copy of or request deletion of your personal information by logging into your account or by contacting us at the contact information below. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. In certain circumstances we may be required by law to retain your personal information, or may need to retain your personal information in order to continue providing a service. 

Wildbit, LLC acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. Wildbit has no direct relationship with your customers or end users whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct their query to the Wildbit, LLC’s Client (the data controller). If requested to remove data we will respond within a reasonable timeframe. In certain circumstances we may be required by law to retain your personal information, or may need to retain your personal information in order to continue providing a service. 

You may also have the right to make a GDPR complaint to the relevant Supervisory Authority. A list of Supervisory Authorities is available here: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm>  

## 7\. Your Choices with respect to the information

_Promotional Email communication:_ You may sign-up to receive email or newsletters or other communications from us. If you would like to discontinue receiving this information, you may update your email preferences by using the “Unsubscribe” link found in emails we send to you or by contacting us at the contact information below. 

_Google Analytics:_ see [http://www.google.com/policies...](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) for information about how Google uses the information provided to Google Analytics and how you can control the information provided to Google. To prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, you can download the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on for Google Analytics which can be found [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

## 8\. Data Retention 

We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. In certain circumstances we may be required by law to retain your personal information, or may need to retain your personal information in order to continue providing a service. 

Even if you delete your account, keep in mind that the deletion by our third party providers may not be immediate and that the deleted information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time. 

## 9 Policy Regarding Children 

The Services are not directed to children under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 16. If you are under 16, please do not use the Services and do not provide any personal information to us. If you become aware that a child under 16 has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [support@postmarkapp.com](mailto:support@postmarkapp.com). If you are a California resident under the age of 18 and you wish to remove publicly available content, please contact us at [support@postmarkapp.com](mailto:support@postmarkapp.com) with the subject line “California Eraser”. 

## 10\. Transfers of information not from the EEA 

To the extent that personal information is transferred to the United States from countries other than countries within the European Economic Area and Switzerland, including personal information that is transferred from Canada, we employ similar safeguards such as selecting third party vendors carefully, ensuring personal information will be used and disclosed only as set out in this privacy policy and that it is protected by appropriate security safeguards. 

However, in connection with these transfers of personal information, your personal information may be subject to privacy laws that may not provide the same protection as your country of residence. For example, government entities in such other countries may have certain rights to access your personal information. By using this Site or using our Service that this privacy notice relates to you are consenting to this transfer of your personal information. 

## 11\. Browser Do Not Track

The Services honor and enforce Do Not Track preferences. Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference you can set in your web browser to indicate that you do not want certain information about your webpage visits collected across websites when you have not interacted with that service on the page. For all the details, including how to turn on Do Not Track, visit [donottrack.us](http://donottrack.us/). 

## 12\. Changes to This Privacy Policy 

We may need to update this policy from time to time. Unless otherwise required by law, we will notify you before we make such changes and give you an opportunity to review them before they go into effect. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

## 13\. Privacy Questions / Feedback

If you have questions or concerns about Wildbit’s Privacy Policy please contact us at [privacy@wildbit.com](mailto:privacy@wildbit.com) or 225 Chestnut St., Philadelphia, PA, 19106. Phone: 215-203-0488.
